allbud.com 2015-03-20

# AllBud.com | MMJ Dispensary Locator and Strain Resource - Privacy Policy

#### _PRIVACY POLICY_

Last updated on _July 3, 2014_. This Privacy Policy is effective immediately for users.

This Privacy Policy describes our policies on the collection, use, and disclosure of information about you in connection with your use of our websites, mobile applications and related services ("Site"). The terms "we", "us", and "Allbud.com" refer to AB Resources, LLC, a Nevada company. When you use the Site, you consent to our collection, use, and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy.

 _1\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT_

We may store the information you submit to or through the Site, as well as information we collect in connection with your use of the Site.

We use the information to fulfill your requests, provide the Site’s functionality, improve the Site’s quality, personalize your experience, track usage of the Site, provide feedback to businesses that are listed on the Site, display relevant advertising, provide customer support, message you, back up our systems and allow for disaster recovery, enhance the security of the Site, and comply with legal obligations.

Among the information we collect, please note: 

  1. _Account Information:_ If you create an account on the Site, we may store and use your full name, email address, user name and other information you may provide with your account. The personal information you submit through the registration process will not be publicly displayed. The information you submit through contact clinic forms on the Site is not stored or used. 
  2. _Communications:_ When you sign up for an account or subscribe to our newsletter, you are opting in to receive emails from Allbud.com itself and third parties that send email on behalf of Albud.com. You cannot opt out of receiving certain administrative or legal notices from Allbud.com. When you submit information through a contact clinic form on the Site you are opting in to receive emails from the recipient. 
  3. _Site Activity:_ We may store information about your use of the Site, such as your search activity, the pages you view, the date and time of your visit, your geographic location, and the businesses you visit from the Site. We also may store information that your computer or mobile device provides to us in connection with your use of the Site, such as your browser type, type of computer or mobile device, browser language, IP address, mobile carrier, unique device identifier, location, and requested and referring URLs. 

_2\. COOKIES_

We, and third parties with whom we partner, may use cookies, web beacons, local shared objects (sometimes called "flash cookies"), HTML5, local storage and similar technology in connection with your use of the Site and third party websites ("Cookies"). Cookies are small data files that may have unique identifiers, and reside, among other places, on your computer or mobile device, in emails we send to you, and on our web pages. Cookies may transmit information about you and your use of the Site, such as your browser type, search preferences, data relating to advertisements that have been displayed to you or that you have clicked on, and the date and time of your use. Cookies may be persistent or stored only during an individual session. Types of Cookies used on the Site include Processes, Authentication, Security and Compliance, Preferences, Notifications and Analytics.

Managing Cookies:

It may be possible to disable some (but not all) cookies through your device or browser settings, but doing so may affect your ability to use the Site. The method for disabling cookies may vary by device and browser, but can usually be found in preferences or security settings.

 _3\. THIRD PARTIES_

We may share information about you with third parties as follows:

  1.  _Aggregate Information:_ We may share user information in the aggregate with third parties, such as advertisers and third party businesses. For example, we may disclose the number of users that have been exposed to, or have clicked on, advertisements. 
  2. _Business Transfers:_ We may share information from or about you with subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control, in which case we will require them to honor this Privacy Policy. If another company acquires Allbud.com or all or substantially all of our assets, that company will possess the same information, and will assume the rights and obligations with respect to that information as described in this Privacy Policy. 
  3. _Businesses on the Site:_ We may share information from or about you and your use of the Site (such as which businesses you have visited) with businesses on the Site. 
  4. _Investigations:_ We may investigate and disclose information from or about you if we have a good faith belief that such investigation or disclosure is (a) reasonably necessary to comply with legal process and law enforcement instructions and orders, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on us; (b) helpful to prevent, investigate, or identify possible wrongdoing in connection with the Site; or (c) protect our rights, reputation, property, or that of our users, affiliates, or the public. 
  5. _Links:_ The Site may contain links to unaffiliated third party websites. Except as set forth herein, we do not share your personal information with them, and are not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy policies on all such third party websites. 
  6. _Third Party Services:_ The Site is using Google Maps APIs; the Google privacy policy can be found here: <http://www.google.com/privacy.html> and is incorporated by reference. The Site uses Google Analytics to understand how our visitors use the Site, you can learn more about how Google Analytics collects and processes data here: <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>. 

_4\. DATA RENTENTION AND ACCOUNT TERMINATION_

In the event you terminate your account we may retain information about you for the purposes authorized under this Privacy Policy unless prohibited by law. For example, we may retain information to prevent, investigate, or identify possible wrongdoing in connection with the Site or to comply with legal obligations. Please note that businesses cannot remove their business listings by terminating their accounts.

To terminate your account, email us at [budtender@allbud.com](mailto:budtender@allbud.com?Subject=Terminate%20My%20Account).

 _5\. CHILDREN_

The Site is intended for adult audiences and is not directed to children under 18. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 18. If you become aware that a child has provided us with personal information without parental consent, please contact us. If we become aware that a child under 18 has provided us with personal information without parental consent, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account.

 _6\. SECURITY_

We follow generally accepted industry standards, including SSL, to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or via mobile device, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

 _7\. DISPUTE RESOLUTION:_

If you believe that Allbud.com has not adhered to this Privacy Policy you may email us at [legal@allbud.com](mailto:legal@allbud.com?Subject=Privacy%20Policy).

 _8\. JURISDICTION_

The information we obtain from or about you may be processed and stored in the United States, which may provide for different data protection rules than the country in which you reside. 

_9\. MODIFICATIONS TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY_

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the Privacy Policy will govern our use of information about you. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by email or by posting a notice on the Site prior to the effective date of the changes. By continuing to access or use the Site after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.
